练习 1-6：纯声音。这一次，请边听边模仿说话者，同时
Exercise 1-6, pure sound. This time, listen and imitate the speaker while
读第一行。注意第二行已经把它为你拼写出来了。
reading the first line. Notice that in the second line, it's spelled out for you.
把这些声音和新的字母对应起来，包括会变成 D 的 T。这个
Match the sounds with the new letters, including the T that turns into a D. This
只是一个临时过渡；等你真正掌握这些声音之后，你就会
is only a temporary transition, and once you've really learned the sounds, you'll
回到常规拼写。语调已经为你标出来了，所以继续
go back to regular spelling. The intonation is marked for you, so continue
with the physical tapping and snapping. One, ba blast is job. Two, Scott tada lot.
第三，don bada bike。视觉提示：如果你能看到它，就掌握它了。而且如果
Three, don bada bike. Your visual. If you see it, you've got it. And it's hard to
你看不到这些声音，也就很难捕捉到它们。现在你已经看到这些句子
catch sounds if you can't get a look at them. Now that you've seen the sentences
以正确英语形式呈现，就可以用视觉表征来加深印象，换个花哨的说法，
in proper English, you can imprint with the visual representation, a fancy way of
也就是拼写。
saying spelling.